[
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 17,
		"Task": "99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_00_B",
		"AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_01",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT3_Legwear_20",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 17,
		"Task": "99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99A_Grace_00",
		"AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_01B",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_01",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_02_Rumors",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 17,
		"Task": "99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
		"AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_02",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_01B",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT2",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_complete_available_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 19,
		"Task": "99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
		"AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_03",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_02",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_complete_available_response_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 20,
		"Task": "99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99A_Adiana_00",
		"AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_04",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_03",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "amethystcutt2",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_complete_available_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 20,
		"Task": "99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99A_Adiana_00",
		"AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_05",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_04",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT3_Chestwear_20",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_complete_available_response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 20,
		"Task": "99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99A_Adiana_00",
		"AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_06",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_05",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT2",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 21,
		"Task": "99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99A_Adiana_00",
		"AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_07",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_06",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "Azoth_Vessel",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 21,
		"Task": "99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
		"AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_08",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_07",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT3_Footwear_20",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 21,
		"Task": "99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
		"AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_08",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT3_Handwear_20",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_complete_available_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 23,
		"Task": "99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
		"AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_10",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_09",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_proposal_prompt_next",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_complete_available_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 24,
		"Task": "99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
		"AchievementId": "99_MSQ_19",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT2",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 24,
		"Task": "99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99A_Captain",
		"AchievementId": "99_MSQ_19a",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_19",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_complete_available_response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 25,
		"Task": "99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_02",
		"AchievementId": "99_MSQ_20",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_19a",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT3_Chestwear_30",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_start_prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_proposal_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_proposal_c_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 25,
		"Task": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_02",
		"AchievementId": "99_MSQ_21",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_20",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT3",
		"ItemRewardQty": 10,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_start_prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_proposal_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_complete_available_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_15_Ritual",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 25,
		"Task": "99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_02",
		"AchievementId": "99_MSQ_22",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_21",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"NOTE": "Soul Trial"
	}
]